<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<imdb_movies>

<movie>
    <name><b><u>Glass</u></b></name>
    <img src="https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTU0NjQ4MjIyOV5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwNTg5ODU5NTM@._V1_SX1777_CR0,0,1777,744_AL_.jpg">
    <br>
    <actors>
    Actors:
        <ul>
            <li>James McAvoy</li>
            <li>Bruce Willis</li>
            <li>Samuel L. Jackson</li>
        </ul>
    </actors>
    <description>
   Security guard David Dunn uses his supernatural abilities to track Kevin Wendell Crumb, 
   a disturbed man who has twenty-four personalities.
   </description>
</movie>

<br>
<br>

<movie>
    <name><b><u>Aquaman</u></b></name>
    <br>
    <img src="https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMjE2MDg1OTg5NF5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwMTIwMTg0NjM@._V1_SX1777_CR0,0,1777,999_AL_.jpg">
    <actors>
    Actors:
        <ul>
            <li>Jason Momoa</li>
            <li>Amber Heard</li>
            <li>Willem Dafoe</li>
    </ul>
    </actors>
    <description>
    Arthur Curry, the human-born heir to the underwater kingdom of Atlantis, 
    goes on a quest to prevent a war between the worlds of ocean and land.
    <br>
    Arthur Curry, half human half from Atlantis, goes on a trip of a lifetime. 
   Not only does this adventure compel him to come to terms with his real identity, but it also 
   forces him to discover whether he is entirely worthy of fulfilling his own destiny: becoming a 
   king. Written by Domingo Alvarez
    </description>
</movie>

<br>
<br>

<movie>
    <name><b><u>I Am Legend</u></b></name>
    <br>
    <img src="https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTg5NTk5MDQ1Ml5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTYwNjgzNTg2._V1_.jpg"> 
    <br>
    <actors>
    Actors:
        <ul>
            <li>Will Smith</li>
            <li>Alice Barge</li>
            <li>Charlie Tahan</li>
        </ul>
    </actors>
    <description>
    Years after a plague kills most of humanity and transforms the rest into monsters, 
    the sole survivor in New York City struggles valiantly to find a cure.
    <br>
    Robert Neville is a scientist who was unable to stop the spread of the terrible virus that 
    was incurable and man-made. Immune, Neville is now the last human survivor in what is left of 
    New York City and perhaps the world. For three years, Neville has faithfully sent out daily 
    radio messages, desperate to find any other survivors who might be out there. 
    But he is not alone. Mutant victims of the plague -- The Infected -- lurk in the shadows... 
    watching Neville's every move... waiting for him to make a fatal mistake. Perhaps mankind's last, 
    best hope, Neville is driven by only one remaining mission: to find a way to reverse the effects 
    of the virus using his own immune blood. But he knows he is outnumbered... and quickly running out 
    of time. Written by Warner Bros. Pictures
    </description>
</movie>

</imdb_movies>
